

About Me

I Am an enthusiastic and passionate WEB And Mobile Application Developer From University Of Karachi having a special interest in Frontend technologies and experience of building Web and Mobile applications with JavaScript / Reactjs / React Native / Nodejs and some other cool libraries and frameworks. I pursue perfection in my every Practice projects. I put dedication in every project that I do. And I hope my dedication will help me to explore my expertise, and to boost up my career plan.



Contact Info

- 0341-2848955
- huzefatariq5@gmail.com
- Metroville Orangi Town, Karachi
- () huzefatariq1



Educational Profile

Jan 2019 - Continoue (8th semester)

BS Computer Science (BSCS)

University Of Karachi (UBIT)

Gpa: 2.73

2015-2017

H.Sc(Pre-Engineering)

Private Candidate (Board Of Secondary Education Karachi)

Percentage: 75.45%

2013-2015

Matric(Science Group)

The Educators

Percentage: 83.15%



Working Experience

Renexcode

Nov 2021 - jan 2022

MERN & React Native Developer

- Use my extensive experience with front end development to define the structure and components for the project, making sure they are
- Keep the code quality high reviewing code from other developers and suggesting improvements.
- Interact with the designer to suggest changes and to make sure the view he has about the design is translated into actual functionality.



Esspfa

Nov 2021 - jan 2022

Trainee Front-end Developer

- Design easy user interfaces and great user ex periences for the digital platforms of small compa
- Vanilla Javascript development with DOM Man ipulation and styling with CSS3.
- Blogging website and E-commerce developme nt with Dashboard.

